Lumbard, Eliot H.; Papers apap071
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Other Public Service, Professional Associations and Organizations, 1952-2006; 7.5 cubic ft.
  - MD- Mathias Campaign-Juvenile Delinquency-Report- and Notes, 1968; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MD- Mathias Campaign- "Organized Crime and National Crime", 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - MD - Mathias Campaign- Narcotics-Report-Recommendations, 1968; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - MD, Mathias Campaign - Staff Lists and Memos, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - MD- Mathias Campaign- Street Crime Press Releases and Notes, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - MD, Mathias Campaign, T.V- Radio Promotions - Notes, 1968; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Merchant Marine Academy, Battle Standard Dinners, Commencement, and Alumni Activities, 1995-1996; 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Merchant Marines, Kings Point in Depth: Folios 1 and 2, 2006; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders Press Releases (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders Press Releases (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency (NCCD), 1967; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - National Criminal Justice Organizations, 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - National Moot Court Competition, 1954-1957 (Oversized 21)
  - National Moot Court Competition, 1959-1964 (Oversized 21)
  - NJ, Crime Control, Corresp., Memos, and Notes, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - NJ, Crime Control- Reports and Testimonies, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - NJ, Criminal Justice Reform, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - NJ, Gov. Hughes' Messages to the Legislature, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - NJ, Legislative Committee Studying Criminal Justice Consultant, 1968; 1974; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - NJ- Office of Sheriff - Activities - Reports and Statements, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - NJ, Report of EHL Regarding the System of Administering Criminal Justice in Essex County, NJ, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - NJ, Report of the Joint Legislative Committee to Study Crime and the System of Criminal Justice in NJ, Notes, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - NJ, Report on Senate No. 897, Electronic Surveillance, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - NJ, Wiretapping, Electronic Surveillance and Governmental Corruption, 1968; 1971-1992; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - NYC Police Foundation, A Day in the Life at the NYPD, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - NYC Police Foundation Annual Report and Partners, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - NYC Police Foundation Benefit Dinner, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - NYC Police Foundation Board of Trustee Meeting Minutes, Memos, Financial Statements and Heroes, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Bramshil Scholarship, 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYC Police Foundation Commissioner Benjamin Ward/ Jeremy Travis, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Community and Cops Magazines, 1992; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYC Police Foundation Corresp. and Agendas, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYC Police Foundation Correspondence and Agendas, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Corresp., Articles, and Memos, 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NYC Police Department, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Directories, 1973; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Executive Conon, Meeting Minutes, Memos, and Remarks, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Report and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Report and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - NYC Police Foundation Financial Statements, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NYC Police Foundation, "Impart of Indirectly Related Organizational Variables" (1 of 1), Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYC Police Foundation, "Impart of Indirectly Related Organizational Variables" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Newsletters, Corresp, and Pamphlets, 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYC Police Foundation, NYPD, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Pamphlets, 1975-1985; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NYC Police Foundation Planning Committee Corresp. and Memos, 1988-1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - NYC Police Foundation Planning Committee Corresp. and Memos, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - NYC Police Foundation Police Academy Museum, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Police Student's Law Guide (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Police Student's Law Guide (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Press Packet, 1981; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Press Packet, 1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Publications, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Report and Respect, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Report to the Commissioner: An Eval of Recruit Level Sensitivity and Integrity Training at the NYC Police Academy, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Search Committee for Executive Director, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Seminar on Police Roles in Crime Prevention: Problems and Solutions in Japan and the U.S., 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NYC Police Foundation, "The 100 Hats of Officer Jones" Campaign, 1974; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - NYC Police Foundation, Trust Magazine, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NYC Police Foundation, 25 Years in Retrospective, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NYC Review Board Conference Recommendations and Proposed Amendments to the Weiss Bill, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NYSBA, Comments Regarding the Desirability of Recommendations to the Appellate Divisions the Rules of Professional Conduct, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NYSBA, Special Committee to Consider Adoption of ABA Model Rules of Professional Conduct (1 of 2), 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - NYSBA Special Committee to Consider Adoption of ABA Model Rules of Professional Conduct (2 of2), 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NYS Delegation to the Republication National Convention Booklet, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NYS Division of Criminal Justice, Drug Abuse Resistance Education (DARE) Initiative Program Descrip./Progress, ca. 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NYS Division of Criminal Justice Services, Criminal Justice Legislative Summary, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - NYS Law Enforcement Accreditation Program, Annual Reports and Standards Manual, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, "An Analysis of the NYS Maritime Museum Block in NYC, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, "A Compilation of Historical + Architectural Data on the NYS Maritime Block in NYC, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Directory, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Feasibility Report, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Museum Consultant's Narrative Report, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Preliminary Plan, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Preliminary Report and Proposal Prepared by NYS Historic Trust Staff, 1970; 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - NYS Maritime Museum, Preliminary Report to the Planning Committee, Correspondence and Articles, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NYS Maritime Museum Schermerhorn Row Block Preliminary Historic Structure Report, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NYS Maritime Museum and South Street Seaport Museum Consolidation, 1979-1981; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NYS Senate Committee on Investigations, Taxation + Govt. Operation News, 1980; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - New York Young Republican Club, Inc. Urban Leadership Symposium Paper Presented, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ocean Liner Museum, 1983-1986; 2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Ocean Liner Museum, Corresp. and Pamphlets, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Office of Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - The Olmsted Condominium, Financial Statements, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Organized Crime Control Council, Organized Crime Awareness Pre Study, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Pennsylvania Bar Association, Application to Join, Corresp., and Pamphlets, 1983-1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Police Corruption: A Perspective on its Nature and Control, Press Release, and Article, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Police Executive's Organized Crime Enforcement Handbook, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - The President's Commission on Law Enforcement and Admin. of Justice, Report, Articles, and Notes, 1966-1968; Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - President's Commission on Law Enforcement and Admin. of Justice, Task Force Reports, 1967; Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Report- "The Administration of Criminal Justice" by J. Edward Lumbard, Police Department NYC Press Releases, Various Correspondence and Reports, 1963; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Report of the Special Committee to Consider Adoption of ABA Model Rules of Professional Conduct, 1984 December 12 (Oversized 21)
  - Republican Coordinating Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Crime and Delinquency- A Republican Response Draft, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Republican Coordinating Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Statement of David Maxwell, Chairman, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Press Releases, Correspondence, and Reports, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Committee for Republican Research Press Releases and Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Press Releases and Reports (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Press Releases and Reports (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Press Releases, Reports, Notes, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Republican National Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Reports, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Republican Coordinating Committee Task Force on Crime and Delinquency, Reports on Crime Control, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Republican Coordinating Committee Task Force on the Functions of Fed., State, and Local, Gov't, New Directions for Urban America, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - State of New Jersey: Joint Legislative Committee to Study Crime and the System of Criminal Justice, 1968 (Oversized 19)
  - State of New Jersey: Joint Legislative Committee to Study Crime and the System of Criminal Justice - Volume 1, 1968-1969 (Oversized 19)
  - State of New Jersey: Joint Legislative Committee to Study Crime and the System of Criminal Justice - Volume 2, 1968-1969 (Oversized 20)
  - Suffolk County Police Dept. Founding Notes, Corresp. And Charts, 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Supreme Court Appellate Division, First Department, Departmental Disciplinary Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Supreme Court Appellate Division, First Dept., Departmental Disciplinary Committee, Report on Petitions for Reinstatement, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Trinity Episcopal Schools Corporation, Court Case and Corresp., 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Trinity-Pawling School Pamphlet, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Trinity School, Corresp. about Housing, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Trinity School Directories, 1968; Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Publications: Harm to Each Other: Crime and Crime Control in America, 1956-1996; 11.6 cubic ft.
  This series contains several years of research material and drafts of an unpublished manuscript Harm to Each Other: Crime and Crime Control in America. The research encompasses a wide variety of subjects including street crimes, organized crime, juvenile delinquency, racial issues, police departments, courts and law, parole, citizen action, and federal, state, and local government interaction.
  - Book Proposal for Crime Control, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Book Title Ideas, 1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Drafts: Chapter 1-16, 1967 August (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Drafts: Chapter 1, "Patterns", 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Chapter 4-9, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Chapter 5, "The President's Commission and Chapter 2 "The Report Card", 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Both chapters were abandoned.
  - Drafts: Chapter 10, "Drunkenness: The Revolving Door", 1968 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Drafts: Chapter 10-13, ca. 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Drafts: Chapter 12-17 (1 of 2), ca. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Drafts: Chapter 12-17 (2 of 2), ca. 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Drafts: Chapter 12, "The Maze: Our Criminal Justice System" (1 of 2), 1968 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Drafts: Chapter 12, "The Maze: Our Criminal Justice System" (2 of 2), 1968 March (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Drafts: Chapter 12, "The Maze: Our Criminal Justice System", Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Becomes chapter 6.
  - Drafts: Chapter 14-18 and the Appendices, ca. 1968 September (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Drafts: Chapter 18, "The Dike," Outlines, 1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Roots: Crime Causation," Handwritten, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Corrosion: Organized Crime" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Corrosion: Organized Crime" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "The Flood of Diversity" and Section I, 1968; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Internal Combustion", ca. 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Drafts, Chapter Titled "Juvenile Delinquency", Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Lost Focus: Law and Courts", Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Man's Hope of Redemption", Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Narcotics and Dangerous Drugs", Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Drafts: Chapter Titled "Street Crimes", 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Drafts: Correspondence about the Book, 1967-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Drafts: Correspondence of the Chapter Titled Lost Focus: Law and Courts (2 drafts), 1968-1969; 1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Drafts: Edited by Harper's Magazine (1 of 4), 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Drafts: edited by Harper's Magazine (2 of 4), 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Drafts: edited by Harper's Magazine (3 of 4), 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Drafts: edited by Harper's Magazine (4 of 4), 1969 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (1 of 4), 1969 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (2 of 4), 1969 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (3 of 4), 1969 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (4 of 4), 1969 November 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (1 of 4), 1969 November (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (2 of 4), 1969 November (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (3 of 4), 1969 November (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Drafts: Harm to Each Other (4 of 4), 1969 November (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Table of Contents, Chapters 1-18 and Appendices (1 of 3), 1968 November (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Table of Contents, Chapters 1-18 and Appendices (2 of 3), 1968 November (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Drafts: Table of Contents, Chapters 1-18 and Appendices (3 of 3), 1968 November (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Drafts: Third Volume, Chapters 13-18 and the Appendix, 1968 September (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (1 of 10), Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (2 of 10), Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (3 of 10), Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (4 of 10), Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (5 of 10), Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (6 of 10), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (7 of 10), Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (8 of 10), Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (9 of 10), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Various Chapters (10 of 10), Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Chapters 1-9 (1 of 2), 1968 September (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Chapters 1-9 (2 of 2), 1968 September (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Chapters 1-12, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front Matter and Chapter 1, 1968 March (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1-18 (1 of 6), 1969 November (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1-18 (2 of 6), 1969 November (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1-18 (3 of 6), 1969 November (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1 -18 (4 of 6), 1969 November (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1-18 (5 of 6), 1969 November (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Drafts: Volume 1, Front and End Matter and Chapters 1-18 (6 of 6), 1969 November (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Drafts: Volumes I and II (1 of 4), Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Drafts: Volumes I and II (2 of 4), Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Drafts: Volumes I and II (3 of 4), Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Drafts: Volumes I and II (4 of 4), Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Draft, Vol. I and Reference Material, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Editor's Comments and Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Future Research (1 of 2), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Future Research (2 of 2), 1963-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "Key Notes on Major Chapter Issues", 1963-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Notes and Drafts of Preface, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Notes- Several, 1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Notes on Technique, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Outlines and Summaries, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Outlines for Various Chapters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Prologue Notes and Research, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Beggars and Panhandlers, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Burglary, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," California Crime Statistics and Reports (1 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," California Crime Statistics and Reports (2 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," California Crime Statistics and Reports (3 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Collins Case, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Compensation of Victims, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 1- "Street Crimes," Crime Rate, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Crime Statistics, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Crime Statistics, 1968; Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Crime Statistics- Methodology, 1963-1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Fences/ Pawnshops, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Forgery, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," General, 1968-1970; Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Graphs, Flow Charts, Cartoons, 1967; Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Homicide, 1961-1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Homosexuality, 1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Larceny, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Newsclippings, Journal Articles, 1963; 1965; 1968-1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Notes, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Notes, News Clippings, Press Releases, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Notes and Outlines, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Ongoing, 1967-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Press Releases, NYC Crime Stats and NYPD, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Professional Crime, 1963-1968; Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 1- "Street Crimes," Prostitution, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Public Opinion, 1966-1968; Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Race and Crime, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Robbery, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Shoplifting, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," TV Violence, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Vehicle-Auto Theft, 1964-1970; Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Victimology, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Washington, D.C. Crime, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Washington D.C. and Maryland Crime Statistics, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Research: Chapter 1 - "Street Crimes," Women and Crime, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Research: Chapter 2 - "Organized Crime: Corrosion", 1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Research: Chapter 3 - "Narcotics and Dangerous Drugs", 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Research: Chapter 4 - "White Collar Crime," Newsclippings, Speeches, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Research: Chapter 5 - "The Flood of Diversity", 1969-1970; Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Research: Chapter 5 - "The Flood of Diversity," Chicago - 1968 Democratic Convention (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Research: Chapter 5 - "The Flood of Diversity," Chicago Police Department, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Research: Chapter 5 - "The Flood of Diversity," The Ghetto, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Research: Chapter 5 - "The Flood of Diversity," Harlem - 125th Street Area - Rev. Oberia Dempsey, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Criminal Justice System Finances, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," General, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Myths, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Our Crime Control Apparatus, History/Development of System, 1964; 1967; Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Our Crime Control Apparatus, Jurisdictional Maze and System, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Our Crime Control Apparatus, Newsclippings and Notes, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," Our Crime Control Apparatus Outlines, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Research: Chapter 6 - "The Maze," System Discretion, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)